[
  {
    "text": "We received a wire transfer instruction from Akeem Nixon (email: cgarcia@example.com, phone: +1 514 470 8653) to move $85,120.00 from Royal Bank of Canada account 36724-016-8982593 to Deryck Rodriguez at LAURENTIAN BANK. Beneficiary account is 29323-030-9781141 and SWIFT code is SVNSCAM3. Beneficiary email: kimberlyjohnson@example.org. A case number has been assigned for tracking purposes. A follow-up communication will be sent within two business days.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        45,
        56,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        184,
        200,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        65,
        84,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        309,
        336,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        93,
        108,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        163,
        180,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        244,
        261,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        134,
        154,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        204,
        219,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        280,
        288,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        118,
        128,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This letter confirms that HSBC Canada has completed the mandatory customer identification process for Maxton                         Price. Our records show their residential address as 5482 Hawkins Curve, London, ON K5B 5M1 and their date of birth as 23/06/2001. The social insurance number 223-720-149 has been verified. For correspondence, please use kadams@example.com or +1 431 676 9965. The account number assigned is 68686-039-1037367, branch transit 68040-030. Internal reference: RAW-49422318. This filing is made pursuant to FINTRAC reporting obligations.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        102,
        138,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        354,
        372,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        376,
        391,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        186,
        224,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        292,
        303,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        252,
        262,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        26,
        37,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        424,
        441,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        458,
        467,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        217,
        224,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "The compliance team at TD Bank has been notified by issac bowers of potential suspicious activity involving Deanne Herring. Account 56386-002-4461182 received $211,786.00 CAD in unusual deposits. Subject located at 1260 Morrow Roads, Barrie, ON N5L 7R3 with contact details 514.363.3497 and fcross@example.org. SIN 330-463-865 confirmed on file. Ref: YXE-94924871. This case has been referred to FINTRAC. Disclosure is limited to authorized personnel only. Follow-up action required within two business days.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        108,
        122,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        52,
        64,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        291,
        309,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        274,
        286,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        215,
        252,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        315,
        326,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        23,
        30,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        132,
        149,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        159,
        174,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        245,
        252,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Transfer authorization MHL-86501976: Aurelio Martin has requested that CAD 90,813.00 be transferred from account 74408-010-1239473 at Meridian Credit Union to Mathilde Foster. Destination bank is National Bank of Canada, account 25338-004-7100567, SWIFT AKCCCAYT. Contact the sender at 604.654.8409 or dawnwalker@example.org for queries. Beneficiary contact: fflores@example.org. Postal reference: M3Z 7G6. The institution has fulfilled its due diligence obligations. This document is governed by the Bank Act (R.S.C., 1991, c. 46).",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        37,
        51,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        159,
        174,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        302,
        324,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        359,
        378,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        286,
        298,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        113,
        130,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        229,
        246,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        134,
        155,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        196,
        219,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        254,
        262,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        71,
        84,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        398,
        405,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "The know-your-customer review for Hendrik                        Maddox was completed on 2026-03-22. The customer provided a date of birth of 17/05/1990 and a social insurance number of 236-340-596. Their current residential address is recorded as 6825 davis square, mississauga, on m1y 0g6. Contact information on file includes phone number (780) 982-6054 and email address ricardothompson@example.org. The customer holds account 24295-006-5183038 with transit number 10974-006 at BMO. Reference: CGZ-25703218. Flagged for immediate supervisor review. Disclosure is limited to authorized personnel only.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        34,
        71,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        375,
        402,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        342,
        356,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        248,
        290,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        186,
        197,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        142,
        152,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        482,
        485,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        431,
        448,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        469,
        478,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This suspicious activity report was prepared by husayn                         vargas following the identification of unusual transactions on the account of aahana taylor. The subject resides at 4299 Young Inlet, Red Deer, AB T7A 4H6 and has provided 780.799.1085 and rileykimberly@example.com as contact information. Their account 56807-002-1790368 at Canadian Western Bank received deposits totalling $421,648.00 CAD over a short period, which is inconsistent with the customer's known financial profile. SIN on file: 805-506-517. Ref: VSQ-27813711. This report has been filed for FINTRAC review. This record is protected under the Privacy Act of Canada. Personal information is handled in accordance with PIPEDA.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        157,
        170,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        48,
        85,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        268,
        293,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        251,
        263,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        195,
        233,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        520,
        531,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        353,
        374,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        332,
        349,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        403,
        418,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        226,
        233,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "SAR filed by Jadelyn Heath regarding Jashan                         Fleming. The customer, whose social insurance number is 447-539-693, maintains account 83808-004-3085938 at BANK OF NOVA SCOTIA. Their registered address is 9129 Raymond View, Vancouver, BC V1V 3J5. Reachable via juliechang@example.com or 365-743-9019. A total of $186,633.00 in transactions has been flagged. No contact has been made with the subject pending investigation. This filing is made pursuant to FINTRAC reporting obligations. The customer acknowledged receipt of this communication.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        37,
        75,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        13,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        281,
        303,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        307,
        319,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        225,
        265,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        124,
        135,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        176,
        195,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        155,
        172,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        332,
        343,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        258,
        265,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Branch handoff from Jairus                         Escobar to compliance: the customer Haralabos Nichols has a disputed transaction of CAD$151,333 on account 34426-016-7422303 at Royal Bank of Canada. Born 1972-07-22, SIN 378-555-881, address 3776 Yang Island, Vancouver, BC V7G 0E5, postal code V7G 0E5. Contact via (514) 678-8841 or bcampbell@example.com. Card on file: 4864-2146-2644-6845. Ref: CKF-25731613. Immediate review requested.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        87,
        104,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        20,
        58,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        335,
        356,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        317,
        331,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        243,
        282,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        222,
        233,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        206,
        216,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        179,
        199,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        158,
        175,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        372,
        391,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        135,
        146,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        275,
        282,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        296,
        303,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "Case ref UYE-89589697 — zlata martin notes: spoke to Beatrice                       Fuller re account 12211-030-4159986 at Scotiabank. Customer disputing CAD 149,653.00 charge on card 2859-2391-1446-9913. Verified DOB 02 October 1983 and SIN 325-168-640. Address: 8706 Herman Alley, Winnipeg, MB R7E 8G1. Phone: (514) 899-8930. Email: vpotter@example.org. Escalating to fraud team. Risk score has been updated in the customer management system.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        53,
        90,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        24,
        36,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        335,
        354,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        312,
        326,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        264,
        303,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        242,
        253,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        218,
        233,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        123,
        133,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        102,
        119,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        184,
        203,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        154,
        168,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        296,
        303,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Passing this file to Savana Jackson for action. The customer gurpreet davila called to report an unauthorized transfer of $112,749.00 CAD from account 57287-016-8680070 at ATB Financial. They were born on 01 February 1969 and their SIN is 596-650-688. Address on file: 5717 campbell summit, edmonton, ab t6s 0p0. Phone: +1 343 542 1862. Email: greensara@example.org. Card 5073-2576-6052-8987 has also been flagged. Retention period of seven years applies per regulatory requirements.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        61,
        76,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        21,
        35,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        344,
        365,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        320,
        335,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        269,
        311,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        239,
        250,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        205,
        221,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        172,
        185,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        151,
        168,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        372,
        391,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        122,
        137,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Following a routine account review, Fredric Johnson identified transactions warranting further investigation on the account belonging to Duke                           Watkins. The subject's address is 1233 EMILY GATEWAY, VANCOUVER, BC V5P 9Z9, postal code V5P 9Z9. Contact: leemichael@example.net and +1 365 548 2037. Account 64061-039-7811097 at Canadian Western Bank shows activity of CAD 42,213.00. Government ID 241-302-487 has been verified. Ref: HHS-73124028. This report is submitted in compliance with AML regulations. Please retain this document for your records. This report is filed under section 7 of the PCMLTFA.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        137,
        175,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        36,
        51,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        275,
        297,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        302,
        317,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        202,
        243,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        417,
        428,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        348,
        369,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        327,
        344,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        388,
        401,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        236,
        243,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        257,
        264,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Monthly billing summary: LAUCHLIN GEORGE holds account 97540-002-5682128 at National Bank of Canada. Registered address: 7135 Mejia Station, Vancouver, BC V4Y 1E7. Contact email: knightangelica@example.net, phone: 604-622-9082. Payment card 9088-6554-4261-2723 is linked to this account. Balance as of statement date: CAD$87,137. Credit available: CAD 23,226.00. A case number has been assigned for tracking purposes. Telephone verification was used to confirm the customer's identity.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        25,
        40,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        179,
        205,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        214,
        226,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        121,
        162,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        76,
        99,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        55,
        72,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        241,
        260,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        318,
        328,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        348,
        361,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        155,
        162,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "SAR filed by Fizza Roberts regarding jolene                         singh. The customer, whose social insurance number is 851-509-598, maintains account 71182-010-6577986 at Bank of Nova Scotia. Their registered address is 7462 Flynn Parkways, Ottawa, ON N0M 3C0. Reachable via lschultz@example.org or (825) 282-5433. A total of CAD 488,431.00 in transactions has been flagged. No contact has been made with the subject pending investigation. Standard processing times of three to five business days apply. Biometric verification was completed at the branch.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        37,
        73,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        13,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        278,
        298,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        302,
        316,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        223,
        262,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        122,
        133,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        174,
        193,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        153,
        170,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        329,
        343,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        255,
        262,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "As part of our regulatory KYC obligations at Canadian Western Bank, we have verified the identity of jayceon vincent. The customer's date of birth is October 10, 1970, and their social insurance number 117-779-260 has been confirmed. They are currently located at 2664 Obrien Dam, London, ON P6K 9Y6. We have +1 825 557 5783 and martha54@example.com on file. Account 39553-003-8967236 has been opened with transit 93057-016. Identity verification was completed using two pieces of government ID. The customer was informed of the outcome via registered mail.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        101,
        116,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        329,
        349,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        309,
        324,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        264,
        299,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        202,
        213,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        150,
        166,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        45,
        66,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        367,
        384,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        414,
        423,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        292,
        299,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "The branch received a credit application from Jaxxon                         Morales on 2026-03-22. The individual lives at 1037 Pamela Gardens, Edmonton, AB T4J 8J8 and provided 407-825-841 as their government identification. Employment confirmed at castillo plc with declared income of CAD 108,043.00. They have requested CAD$154,100 in financing. Reach them at 780.337.4616 or williamscynthia@example.net. Existing account: 16699-016-9930547 at Meridian Credit Union. Secondary verification has been completed successfully. The customer was cooperative throughout the verification process.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        46,
        84,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        380,
        407,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        364,
        376,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        124,
        165,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        179,
        190,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        448,
        469,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        251,
        263,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        427,
        444,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        324,
        335,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        288,
        302,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        158,
        165,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "A loan application was submitted by oaklynn                        roberts, currently residing at 3322 Glenn Grove, Burnaby, BC V3T 3N3. The applicant was born on 12 April 1995 and their social insurance number is 584-135-233. They are employed at Jenkins Ltd with an annual income of $95,713.00. The requested loan amount is $198,450.00 CAD. Contact details: 416.570.6518 and anthony04@example.org. Their existing account at Desjardins Group is 75748-030-9942933. Unauthorized disclosure of this information is strictly prohibited. The transaction has been placed on hold pending investigation.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        74,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        377,
        398,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        360,
        372,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        98,
        135,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        214,
        225,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        163,
        176,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        426,
        442,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        248,
        259,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        446,
        463,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        326,
        341,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        285,
        295,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        128,
        135,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "Account statement summary for Ramsha Alexander at Scotiabank: account number 86868-039-5726566, card on file 9995-8594-2011-8124. Statement mailed to 2678 smith expressway, halifax, ns b3c 2h5, postal code B3C 2H5. Email notifications sent to toddjohnson@example.net. Phone on file: 780-394-2962. Closing balance this period: CAD$114,902. Available: $19,036.00 CAD. This report is filed under section 7 of the PCMLTFA. Awaiting response from the customer before proceeding.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        30,
        46,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        243,
        266,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        283,
        295,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        150,
        192,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        50,
        60,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        77,
        94,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        109,
        128,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        326,
        337,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        350,
        364,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        206,
        213,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This is to inform Laurentian Bank that I, khaled                         shaffer, have identified a suspicious charge of $2,982.00 on card number 8668-1250-8132-5044 associated with my account 73991-002-3707795. I have not made any such transaction and request an immediate chargeback. My home address is 2615 melanie pine, london, on l4r 6e4 and I can be contacted at 613-663-8086 or via email at wilsonbrittany@example.com. Postal code L4R 6E4.",
    "doc_type": "COMPLAINT_LETTER",
    "entities": [
      [
        42,
        80,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        398,
        424,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        369,
        381,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        305,
        342,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        18,
        33,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        193,
        210,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        146,
        165,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        121,
        130,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        438,
        445,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "Wire transfer request received from shannen taylor via online banking. The customer holds account 58381-039-3300272 at Royal Bank of Canada and wishes to transfer $10,585.00 to Bhavin Baker at CANADIAN WESTERN BANK, account 25829-016-2079683. SWIFT code for receiving institution: HADMCAEA. We have the sender's phone as 204-994-2051 and email as andersonandre@example.net. Beneficiary contact: eddiemurphy@example.com. Postal: T6Y 4G7. Ref: QQO-85311347. Disclosure is limited to authorized personnel only.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        50,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        177,
        189,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        347,
        372,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        395,
        418,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        321,
        333,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        98,
        115,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        224,
        241,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        119,
        139,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        193,
        214,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        281,
        289,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        163,
        173,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        428,
        435,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Report ref EKL-32258229: reyna decker escalated a case involving rosa larsen whose RBC account 88827-030-4677136 shows unusual cash movements of CAD$420,831. The individual lives at 7852 lisa fields, ottawa, on p5a 1k4 and can be contacted at antoniosingleton@example.com or 204.963.2701. Their government-issued SIN is 360-173-287. No prior SAR history on file for this customer. Documentation has been reviewed and approved by branch manager. Secondary verification has been completed successfully.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        65,
        76,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        25,
        37,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        243,
        271,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        275,
        287,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        182,
        218,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        320,
        331,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        83,
        86,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        95,
        112,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        145,
        156,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "Branch authorized wire transfer for shmuel                         jenkins today. Amount: $187,221.00. From account 34651-010-4279383 at scotiabank. To: gwenda fuentes, account 34587-010-8612550, bank bank of nova scotia, swift HVWRCAGK. Sender reachable at 514.394.4284 or diane11@example.com. Beneficiary at marcus16@example.com. The institution has fulfilled its due diligence obligations.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        74,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        153,
        167,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        274,
        293,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        310,
        330,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        258,
        270,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        116,
        133,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        177,
        194,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        137,
        147,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        201,
        220,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        228,
        236,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        90,
        101,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "International transfer on behalf of Jairus Owen to Batool Frazier. Sending CAD 173,866.00 from TD Bank (30364-039-2027531) to Canadian Western Bank (18213-002-4200355). SWIFT: MLCXCAK9. Sender: rebekahbeard@example.net, 204-594-3393. Recipient: tonyarowe@example.com. Ref: YKB-18472076. Postal: K0Z 6N2. The customer acknowledged receipt of this communication. Biometric verification was completed at the branch.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        47,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        51,
        65,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        194,
        218,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        245,
        266,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        220,
        232,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        104,
        121,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        149,
        166,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        95,
        102,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        126,
        147,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        176,
        184,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        75,
        89,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        295,
        302,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Prepared for jaivin chen — Scotiabank account 74805-039-5626659. Statement period: 2026-03-01 to 2026-03-22. Linked card: 5217-1572-4672-1971. Balance: CAD$89,494. Available: CAD 37,615.00. Mailing address on file: 3657 ROBERT CIRCLE, HAMILTON, ON K1V 0E8. Email: kristen59@example.com. Tel: (514) 837-1279. Cross-referenced with existing customer records — no discrepancies found. A copy has been filed in the customer record system.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        13,
        24,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        264,
        285,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        292,
        306,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        215,
        255,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        27,
        37,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        46,
        63,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        122,
        141,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        152,
        162,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        175,
        188,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        248,
        255,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "File update by Verner Mcmahon: account review for eldon wilson completed. Born January 23, 1991. Government ID (SIN): 168-566-826. Lives at 9614 DAVID KNOLL, WINDSOR, ON P8J 6G6. Correspondence to sjones@example.com, calls to +1 604 986 9547. Account 35408-030-8467134 at Desjardins Group flagged for CAD$176,600. Card 7734-5901-3947-7303 suspended pending investigation. Postal: P8J 6G6. Ref: QJH-56950601. The branch manager has been copied on all correspondence. Telephone verification was used to confirm the customer's identity.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        50,
        62,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        15,
        29,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        197,
        215,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        226,
        241,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        140,
        177,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        118,
        129,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        79,
        95,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        272,
        288,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        251,
        268,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        319,
        338,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        301,
        312,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        170,
        177,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        380,
        387,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "A wire transfer request was submitted by devina williams, who holds account 23320-030-4005458 at meridian credit union. The sender can be reached at 365-909-9459 or leah18@example.com. The requested transfer amount is $87,778.00 to be sent to Tremaine Fuller at Canadian Western Bank, account 70978-010-4483978. The receiving institution SWIFT code is VFMBCAGR. Postal code on file: R2W 1B6. Reference: AQM-22224198. Retention period of seven years applies per regulatory requirements. This matter will be reviewed at the next compliance meeting.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        41,
        56,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        243,
        258,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        165,
        183,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        149,
        161,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        76,
        93,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        293,
        310,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        97,
        118,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        262,
        283,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        352,
        360,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        218,
        228,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        383,
        390,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "SAR filed by Zackery Baker regarding TAIMOOR COLEMAN. The customer, whose social insurance number is 643-248-170, maintains account 35001-002-7304131 at TD Bank. Their registered address is 8233 bryan pike, winnipeg, mb r2w 7m0. Reachable via bwu@example.net or 825-812-7051. A total of CAD 312,989.00 in transactions has been flagged. No contact has been made with the subject pending investigation. The matter has been escalated to the relevant department. Subject to the Proceeds of Crime (Money Laundering) and Terrorist Financing Act.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        37,
        52,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        13,
        26,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        243,
        258,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        262,
        274,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        190,
        227,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        101,
        112,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        153,
        160,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        132,
        149,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        287,
        301,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "I spoke with tillie pham today regarding the hold placed on their account. They called in at 587-974-5738 and I verified their date of birth as 1983-12-24 and social insurance number 792-616-970. The customer confirmed their new address as 6560 Maddox Mill, Winnipeg, MB R3W 9C6. Their email is dpatton@example.org. Account 98880-016-3603380 at BMO has a disputed balance of $19,506.00 CAD. I have passed this file to chase                          rivera for follow-up. Ref: AUR-59395647.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        13,
        24,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        418,
        455,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        295,
        314,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        93,
        105,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        240,
        278,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        183,
        194,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        144,
        154,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        345,
        348,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        324,
        341,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        375,
        389,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        271,
        278,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "The branch received a credit application from Dian Hall on 2026-03-22. The individual lives at 9297 Michael Track, Mississauga, ON K1V 5A7 and provided 182-330-247 as their government identification. Employment confirmed at Vega Ltd with declared income of $223,263.00 CAD. They have requested CAD$331,273 in financing. Reach them at (613) 306-9110 or kevindillon@example.net. Existing account: 45971-030-2347123 at BMO. This matter will be reviewed at the next compliance meeting. Disclosure is limited to authorized personnel only.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        46,
        55,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        352,
        375,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        334,
        348,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        95,
        138,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        152,
        163,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        416,
        419,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        224,
        232,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        395,
        412,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        294,
        305,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        257,
        272,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        131,
        138,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "A loan application was submitted by cherry weiss, currently residing at 6780 Hunt Common, Toronto, ON N1R 6X4. The applicant was born on 1962-02-26 and their social insurance number is 806-651-790. They are employed at Rivera Group with an annual income of $174,188.00. The requested loan amount is $167,278.00. Contact details: +1 604 599 2155 and daniel08@example.org. Their existing account at meridian credit union is 74061-004-9907542. This communication is protected under Canadian privacy legislation. The customer acknowledged receipt of this communication.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        48,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        349,
        369,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        329,
        344,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        72,
        109,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        185,
        196,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        137,
        147,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        397,
        418,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        219,
        231,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        422,
        439,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        299,
        310,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        257,
        268,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        102,
        109,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "The following statement covers transactions for the account held by Jeremy                         Stevens at royal bank of canada. The account number is 98789-004-1556791 and the associated card is 7148-9055-7617-1558. Statements are mailed to 1696 DONALD WALL, HAMILTON, ON L6L 9L1 and digital copies sent to rodney39@example.org. Current balance stands at $77,981.00 with CAD 26,995.00 available. Contact: 204.753.9517. Subject to the Proceeds of Crime (Money Laundering) and Terrorist Financing Act. A copy has been filed in the customer record system.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        68,
        106,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        311,
        331,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        409,
        421,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        245,
        283,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        110,
        130,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        154,
        171,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        199,
        218,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        359,
        369,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        375,
        388,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        276,
        283,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "We received a wire transfer instruction from Stella                         Martinez (email: michellemeyer@example.net, phone: 587.405.9981) to move CAD 167,968.00 from BMO account 54660-016-3309314 to PRESLEY HOFFMAN at Meridian Credit Union. Beneficiary account is 69515-039-8332314 and SWIFT code is FLARCAHW. Beneficiary email: ogonzalez@example.net. Case forwarded to the compliance department for further review. Telephone verification was used to confirm the customer's identity.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        45,
        84,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        202,
        217,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        93,
        118,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        332,
        353,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        127,
        139,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        181,
        198,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        267,
        284,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        169,
        172,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        221,
        242,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        303,
        311,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        149,
        163,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "This monthly statement has been prepared for Dillon Scott, whose mailing address is 8543 Hudson Mill, Montreal, QC H9T 9J5. The account holder can be contacted at 647.787.7788 or simpsonyolanda@example.org. Their primary account at CIBC is 34686-003-5391339, with linked card 5530-6462-3737-2661. The closing balance for this period is $44,255.00 CAD, with available credit of CAD$46,347. Supporting documentation is available upon request. The customer has been advised of their rights under PIPEDA.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        45,
        57,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        179,
        205,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        163,
        175,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        84,
        122,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        232,
        236,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        240,
        257,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        276,
        295,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        336,
        350,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        377,
        387,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        115,
        122,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "This memo documents the wire transfer initiated by Emmeline Goodman from RBC account 78306-004-4950532. The transfer of $190,437.00 CAD is destined for Gloria-Jean Cabrera whose account 83051-016-6789641 is held at TD Bank with SWIFT identifier XZSXCA7Y. The originating customer's email is ohensley@example.com and phone is +1 289 790 7376. Beneficiary email on record: shawnmartin@example.com. Disclosure is limited to authorized personnel only. This record is protected under the Privacy Act of Canada.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        51,
        67,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        152,
        171,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        291,
        311,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        371,
        394,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        325,
        340,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        85,
        102,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        186,
        203,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        73,
        76,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        215,
        222,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        245,
        253,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        120,
        135,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Branch staff completed identity verification for Sanad                          Boyle today. The customer confirmed their residential address as 991 Stephanie Village, Mississauga, ON N8L 4L0, postal code N8L 4L0. Date of birth: August 30, 1995. SIN: 599-945-366. Best contact is lhatfield@example.org or 780-672-9140. Account 40285-039-4437473 established at Bank of Nova Scotia, transit 63217-030. No further action is required from the customer at this time. Follow-up action required within two business days.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        49,
        85,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        280,
        301,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        305,
        317,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        145,
        191,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        251,
        262,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        229,
        244,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        360,
        379,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        327,
        344,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        389,
        398,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        184,
        191,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        205,
        212,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "SAR filed by Carlo                          Flores regarding Marguerite Meza. The customer, whose social insurance number is 240-453-571, maintains account 34348-030-4060513 at bmo. Their registered address is 9334 Hunter Parkways, Burnaby, BC V5W 9J5. Reachable via eball@example.com or 289-669-2837. A total of $199,551.00 CAD in transactions has been flagged. No contact has been made with the subject pending investigation. The customer has been advised of their rights under PIPEDA. Escalated to senior compliance officer for sign-off.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        61,
        76,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        13,
        50,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        267,
        284,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        288,
        300,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        210,
        251,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        125,
        136,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        177,
        180,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        156,
        173,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        313,
        328,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        244,
        251,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "File update by Yazan Ferguson: account review for Kanan Avery completed. Born 1985-10-17. Government ID (SIN): 537-938-462. Lives at 2782 Carl Road, Burnaby, BC V6A 3S3. Correspondence to swansonjane@example.org, calls to 289-590-9878. Account 82071-016-3880977 at national bank of canada flagged for $38,409.00. Card 2013-8212-4939-9446 suspended pending investigation. Postal: V6A 3S3. Ref: YCR-56938042. A case number has been assigned for tracking purposes. The institution has fulfilled its due diligence obligations.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        50,
        61,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        15,
        29,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        188,
        211,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        222,
        234,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        133,
        168,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        111,
        122,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        78,
        88,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        265,
        288,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        244,
        261,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        318,
        337,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        301,
        311,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        161,
        168,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        379,
        386,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Hi, I am zehra brown and I bank with Bank of Nova Scotia. There is a charge of CAD 4,990.00 on my statement that I do not recognize on card 8533-4920-7375-8837 under account 78893-030-5577421. I did not make this purchase and want it reversed. Please call me at +1 519 703 8182 or send an email to allison58@example.net. My address is 1152 Craig Landing, Toronto, ON L8G 8B7.",
    "doc_type": "COMPLAINT_LETTER",
    "entities": [
      [
        9,
        20,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        298,
        319,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        262,
        277,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        335,
        374,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        37,
        56,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        174,
        191,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        140,
        159,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        79,
        91,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        367,
        374,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Branch staff completed identity verification for Mahnoor Lee today. The customer confirmed their residential address as 7000 WILLIAM LOAF, BURNABY, BC V6B 1A6, postal code V6B 1A6. Date of birth: 15/01/1995. SIN: 617-736-556. Best contact is cheryl54@example.net or 437-524-2136. Account 58433-030-7048742 established at RBC, transit 82399-004. Retention period of seven years applies per regulatory requirements. The file has been marked as high priority.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        49,
        60,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        242,
        262,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        266,
        278,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        120,
        158,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        213,
        224,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        196,
        206,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        321,
        324,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        288,
        305,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        334,
        343,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        151,
        158,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        172,
        179,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Loan assessment for JASVEEN                        NGUYEN (DOB: 21 September 1952, SIN: 619-997-219): The applicant is employed by cuevas-watson earning CAD 187,990.00 annually and is seeking a personal loan of CAD 404,170.00. They reside at 5070 NICHOLAS HEIGHTS, RED DEER, AB T6K 6M4 and provided hjohnson@example.net and (604) 579-7362 as contact information. Their account 27339-030-8524090 at Meridian Credit Union is in good standing. Internal audit trail has been updated accordingly. The branch manager has been copied on all correspondence.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        20,
        57,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        299,
        319,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        324,
        338,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        242,
        285,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        88,
        99,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        64,
        81,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        398,
        419,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        131,
        144,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        377,
        394,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        211,
        225,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        153,
        167,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        278,
        285,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Account statement summary for HARRISON LE at Canadian Western Bank: account number 10609-016-8789481, card on file 3440-7653-7473-5994. Statement mailed to 1741 Lee Ramp, Toronto, ON P6H 4Y5, postal code P6H 4Y5. Email notifications sent to davidmyers@example.net. Phone on file: +1 204 546 2122. Closing balance this period: $125,541.00. Available: $44,577.00. This matter will be reviewed at the next compliance meeting. Further verification may be required before processing.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        30,
        41,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        241,
        263,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        280,
        295,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        156,
        190,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        45,
        66,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        83,
        100,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        115,
        134,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        326,
        337,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        350,
        360,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        183,
        190,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        204,
        211,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Following a routine account review, talya                          king identified transactions warranting further investigation on the account belonging to khloé mercado. The subject's address is 4127 martha trafficway, calgary, ab t5a 2m2, postal code T5A 2M2. Contact: thompsonlarry@example.net and +1 236 251 6428. Account 42126-016-4010460 at Bank of Nova Scotia shows activity of $129,089.00. Government ID 775-574-744 has been verified. Ref: INM-16100028. This report is submitted in compliance with AML regulations. Electronic records have been updated to reflect the changes. Cross-referenced with existing customer records — no discrepancies found.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        157,
        170,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        36,
        71,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        272,
        297,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        302,
        317,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        197,
        240,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        413,
        424,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        348,
        367,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        327,
        344,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        386,
        397,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        254,
        261,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This letter confirms that Canadian Western Bank has completed the mandatory customer identification process for Darquise Weber. Our records show their residential address as 1560 Laura Hill, Brampton, ON K2B 7S5 and their date of birth as December 13, 1965. The social insurance number 328-321-445 has been verified. For correspondence, please use kbrown@example.com or 343-538-1990. The account number assigned is 67310-002-5172632, branch transit 92633-030. Internal reference: WBA-29657507. This report is filed under section 7 of the PCMLTFA.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        112,
        126,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        348,
        366,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        370,
        382,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        174,
        211,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        286,
        297,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        239,
        256,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        26,
        47,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        415,
        432,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        449,
        458,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        204,
        211,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "International transfer on behalf of girl ortiz to Cory Mathews. Sending $61,473.00 from bmo (15990-016-2488469) to Bank of Nova Scotia (11654-010-8957785). SWIFT: ECCCCAKS. Sender: plang@example.net, +1 437 514 9169. Recipient: bridget23@example.org. Ref: ION-51343977. Postal: M4K 0L4. The customer was informed of the outcome via registered mail. The customer's profile has been updated in the core banking system.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        46,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        50,
        62,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        181,
        198,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        228,
        249,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        200,
        215,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        93,
        110,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        136,
        153,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        88,
        91,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        115,
        134,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        163,
        171,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        72,
        82,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        278,
        285,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "Wire transfer request received from jaxton porter via online banking. The customer holds account 86423-030-1840271 at ROYAL BANK OF CANADA and wishes to transfer CAD 145,248.00 to Zeynep Barrett at HSBC Canada, account 10933-002-2128350. SWIFT code for receiving institution: QNOPCAZV. We have the sender's phone as 780.732.5645 and email as hoodmelissa@example.com. Beneficiary contact: beckkevin@example.org. Postal: R7C 9E8. Ref: PUO-89581408. The institution has fulfilled its due diligence obligations.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        49,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        180,
        194,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        342,
        365,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        388,
        409,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        316,
        328,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        97,
        114,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        219,
        236,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        118,
        138,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        198,
        209,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        276,
        284,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        162,
        176,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        419,
        426,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Dear Adriano                        Hoffman, this is your statement from Scotiabank for account 87342-016-9503859. Your card 2991-8088-8308-3389 shows a closing balance of $28,455.00. Available funds are $31,764.00. We have your address as 9297 Candice Flats, Kitchener, ON L8G 2P1 and your email as whitewesley@example.net. Questions? Call us at +1 778 281 2336. This document is governed by the Bank Act (R.S.C., 1991, c. 46).",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        5,
        43,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        300,
        323,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        347,
        362,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        240,
        281,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        73,
        83,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        96,
        113,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        125,
        144,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        172,
        182,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        204,
        214,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        274,
        281,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "The account held by jimmy baxter at RBC shows the following activity for the current billing period. Account 30825-003-6976431 is associated with card 6079-1543-7576-8579. The account holder resides at 5116 LISA BYPASS, VANCOUVER, BC V3Z 4K1 and can be contacted at 647-821-8564 or tina36@example.net. The postal code on record is V3Z 4K1. Closing balance: CAD 102,072.00. Credit available: CAD 20,400.00. Coordinating with fraud prevention team on this matter.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        20,
        32,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        282,
        300,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        266,
        278,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        202,
        241,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        36,
        39,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        109,
        126,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        151,
        170,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        357,
        371,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        391,
        404,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        234,
        241,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        331,
        338,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Internal compliance report — confidential. Subject: kai                            smith. Prepared by: Ekam Hunter. The subject holds account 50295-004-2403406 at Desjardins Group and resides at 3456 Michael Radial, Windsor, ON M3A 0E1, postal code M3A 0E1. Their SIN is 576-757-589. Transactions totalling CAD 157,847.00 have been flagged as suspicious. Contact information: (365) 340-7109 and masontony@example.com. Reference: NWA-83911449. This record is protected under the Privacy Act of Canada. The institution has fulfilled its due diligence obligations.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        52,
        88,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        103,
        114,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        395,
        416,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        376,
        390,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        195,
        235,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        271,
        282,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        163,
        179,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        142,
        159,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        307,
        321,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        228,
        235,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        249,
        256,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "International transfer on behalf of domenica simpson to Ilyas Scott. Sending $209,147.00 CAD from RBC (12904-039-1279415) to HSBC Canada (71118-003-1712149). SWIFT: YBBSCAWH. Sender: bsantiago@example.com, (519) 538-4688. Recipient: jeremy86@example.com. Ref: DZT-37514534. Postal: K5C 2Z8. The transaction has been placed on hold pending investigation. The customer was informed of the outcome via registered mail.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        52,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        56,
        67,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        183,
        204,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        233,
        253,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        206,
        220,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        103,
        120,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        138,
        155,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        98,
        101,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        125,
        136,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        165,
        173,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        77,
        92,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        282,
        289,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This monthly statement has been prepared for BRADY                          KELLEY, whose mailing address is 8369 leah locks, toronto, on m0y 2n6. The account holder can be contacted at 416.984.2408 or juliaharris@example.org. Their primary account at meridian credit union is 53260-030-3120708, with linked card 9524-5086-8763-8824. The closing balance for this period is CAD$125,446, with available credit of $21,527.00 CAD. All information has been verified against existing records. Further verification may be required before processing.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        45,
        82,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        202,
        225,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        186,
        198,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        109,
        145,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        252,
        273,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        277,
        294,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        313,
        332,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        373,
        384,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        411,
        425,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Hi, I am Daphné Stephens and I bank with Bank of Montreal. There is a charge of $3,126.00 on my statement that I do not recognize on card 8202-6795-1591-7288 under account 67637-004-1790871. I did not make this purchase and want it reversed. Please call me at +1 780 200 3313 or send an email to brownanthony@example.net. My address is 5416 Cook Way, Montreal, QC H8M 2V7.",
    "doc_type": "COMPLAINT_LETTER",
    "entities": [
      [
        9,
        24,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        296,
        320,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        260,
        275,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        336,
        371,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        41,
        57,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        172,
        189,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        138,
        157,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        80,
        89,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        364,
        371,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This letter confirms that Meridian Credit Union has completed the mandatory customer identification process for santina pace. Our records show their residential address as 1537 Cooper Turnpike, Brampton, ON P5W 1E0 and their date of birth as 05/04/1983. The social insurance number 146-234-295 has been verified. For correspondence, please use grahamcaitlin@example.org or 647-302-1964. The account number assigned is 87600-030-9545843, branch transit 31365-002. Internal reference: CHB-11248383. Retention period of seven years applies per regulatory requirements.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        112,
        124,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        344,
        369,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        373,
        385,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        172,
        214,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        282,
        293,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        242,
        252,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        26,
        47,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        418,
        435,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        452,
        461,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        207,
        214,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "The account held by Ryley                          Sandoval at Bank of Nova Scotia shows the following activity for the current billing period. Account 78746-039-3878473 is associated with card 9761-1978-3655-1368. The account holder resides at 2101 wilkinson plains, kitchener, on k2g 1v3 and can be contacted at 437.935.7030 or swilliamson@example.org. The postal code on record is K2G 1V3. Closing balance: $40,610.00. Credit available: CAD$42,175. Follow-up action required within two business days.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        20,
        59,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        330,
        353,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        314,
        326,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        245,
        289,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        63,
        82,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        152,
        169,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        194,
        213,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        410,
        420,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        440,
        450,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        384,
        391,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "International transfer on behalf of madelyn brooks to ANGELA                         JOHNSON. Sending CAD 71,163.00 from BMO (52942-039-7248964) to rbc (16964-003-6267553). SWIFT: ZLCQCA8R. Sender: kleinjeremy@example.org, 647-232-1812. Recipient: joshuahaynes@example.net. Ref: JTQ-71240552. Postal: P1M 8W1. The customer acknowledged receipt of this communication. The customer's profile has been updated in the core banking system.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        36,
        50,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        54,
        92,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        198,
        221,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        248,
        272,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        223,
        235,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        126,
        143,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        153,
        170,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        121,
        124,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        148,
        151,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        180,
        188,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        102,
        115,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        301,
        308,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Monthly billing summary: Alianna                        Gonzalez holds account 66507-004-4606317 at Meridian Credit Union. Registered address: 8953 Christopher Greens, Windsor, ON K3Y 0P7. Contact email: michaelcharles@example.org, phone: 514.979.8753. Payment card 6544-4952-1137-1532 is linked to this account. Balance as of statement date: $33,515.00 CAD. Credit available: $48,380.00 CAD. Electronic records have been updated to reflect the changes. The customer acknowledged receipt of this communication.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        25,
        64,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        204,
        230,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        239,
        251,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        143,
        187,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        100,
        121,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        79,
        96,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        266,
        285,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        343,
        357,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        377,
        391,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        180,
        187,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Internal memo — Kenzie Gill to compliance: Milford Perez (SIN: 735-965-163, DOB: December 11, 1995) contacted the branch regarding unusual activity on account 98585-039-4889750. Total amount flagged: $99,522.00. Customer resides at 3668 moore alley, montreal, qc h6c 4m4, postal H6C 4M4. Reachable at 780.745.1698 or debbie08@example.com. Bank: ATB Financial. Card: 6561-4649-8665-6012. This filing is made pursuant to FINTRAC reporting obligations.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        43,
        56,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        16,
        27,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        317,
        337,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        301,
        313,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        232,
        270,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        63,
        74,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        81,
        98,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        345,
        358,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        159,
        176,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        366,
        385,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        200,
        210,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        279,
        286,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Prepared for Evangeline                     Rice — ATB Financial account 64712-010-9523692. Statement period: 2026-03-01 to 2026-03-22. Linked card: 9903-8019-6107-9154. Balance: CAD$114,548. Available: $38,243.00 CAD. Mailing address on file: 9104 SANDRA CAPE, SURREY, BC V3T 6J7. Email: shari43@example.com. Tel: 613.797.5979. This report is filed under section 7 of the PCMLTFA. Subject to the Proceeds of Crime (Money Laundering) and Terrorist Financing Act.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        13,
        48,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        289,
        308,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        315,
        327,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        244,
        280,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        51,
        64,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        73,
        90,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        149,
        168,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        179,
        190,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        203,
        217,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        273,
        280,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Internal memo — Tomás                          Hodges to compliance: shawnee gibson (SIN: 338-850-746, DOB: 16/04/1982) contacted the branch regarding unusual activity on account 92812-006-9051761. Total amount flagged: CAD$142,954. Customer resides at 8048 bridges lake, edmonton, ab t2g 3n0, postal T2G 3N0. Reachable at 236-353-6660 or shannon17@example.org. Bank: bmo. Card: 9565-1410-7175-9460. The institution has fulfilled its due diligence obligations.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        69,
        83,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        16,
        53,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        339,
        360,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        323,
        335,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        253,
        292,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        90,
        101,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        108,
        118,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        368,
        371,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        179,
        196,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        379,
        398,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        220,
        231,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        301,
        308,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Quick note regarding obaloluwa jackson: flagged transaction of $29,320.00 on account 79081-016-2139884. Customer date of birth is 13/09/1990 and SIN is 478-605-658. They are currently living at 7972 Woods Key, Edmonton, AB T7M 4S9 and can be reached at brian71@example.net or +1 519 616 2218. Their card 1983-4231-9105-2924 at TD Bank is under review. Loree Cox has been assigned to this case. The transaction has been placed on hold pending investigation.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        21,
        38,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        352,
        361,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        253,
        272,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        276,
        291,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        194,
        230,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        152,
        163,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        130,
        140,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        327,
        334,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        85,
        102,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        304,
        323,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        63,
        73,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        223,
        230,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "File update by loralee elliott: account review for Nile                           Thompson completed. Born May 05, 1993. Government ID (SIN): 688-678-890. Lives at 8236 heath glen, burnaby, bc v3n 8p5. Correspondence to gserrano@example.com, calls to 780-418-8623. Account 52033-010-8521781 at Bank of Montreal flagged for CAD$98,294. Card 6725-5791-3654-1947 suspended pending investigation. Postal: V3N 8P5. Ref: TWF-57355463. Internal audit trail has been updated accordingly. The customer has been advised of their rights under PIPEDA.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        51,
        90,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        15,
        30,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        220,
        240,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        251,
        263,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        164,
        200,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        142,
        153,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        107,
        119,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        294,
        310,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        273,
        290,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        340,
        359,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        323,
        333,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        401,
        408,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "A wire transfer request was submitted by zelda                          russell, who holds account 61274-010-6246470 at Bank of Nova Scotia. The sender can be reached at 416-645-8474 or annehamilton@example.org. The requested transfer amount is $105,422.00 CAD to be sent to Kaliopi Jimenez at ROYAL BANK OF CANADA, account 41953-006-4240746. The receiving institution SWIFT code is YGSTCAZF. Postal code on file: M1H 5M6. Reference: LUP-25687742. The customer was informed of the outcome via registered mail. Biometric verification was completed at the branch.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        41,
        79,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        275,
        290,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        186,
        210,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        170,
        182,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        99,
        116,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        324,
        341,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        120,
        139,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        294,
        314,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        383,
        391,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        245,
        260,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        414,
        421,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Our branch manager reviewed the application submitted by byron perry, who works at waters-cantu and earns CAD$226,959 per year. The customer is requesting CAD 175,999.00 and currently banks with Meridian Credit Union under account 42240-003-5014610. Their residential address is 7988 THERESA PARKWAY, LONDON, ON P1R 6N1. SIN on file: 305-179-311. DOB: 27 June 1957. Phone: (519) 334-6016. Email: jessicacooper@example.org. Internal audit trail has been updated accordingly. Cross-referenced with existing customer records — no discrepancies found.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        57,
        68,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        396,
        421,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        373,
        387,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        279,
        319,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        334,
        345,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        352,
        364,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        195,
        216,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        83,
        95,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        231,
        248,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        155,
        169,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        106,
        117,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        312,
        319,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Quick note regarding Elouise Lawson: flagged transaction of CAD 108,221.00 on account 14936-006-8983125. Customer date of birth is January 08, 1980 and SIN is 279-524-973. They are currently living at 5246 Michael Valley, Hamilton, ON L8E 3V0 and can be reached at ydyer@example.com or (613) 732-9621. Their card 6346-3107-6900-9750 at BMO is under review. Thatcher Ward has been assigned to this case. Flagged for immediate supervisor review.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        21,
        35,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        357,
        370,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        265,
        282,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        286,
        300,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        201,
        242,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        159,
        170,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        131,
        147,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        336,
        339,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        86,
        103,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        313,
        332,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        60,
        74,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        235,
        242,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "This memo documents the wire transfer initiated by jaxsen williams from Royal Bank of Canada account 67011-002-9786532. The transfer of $111,837.00 is destined for Aviana Palmer whose account 94541-004-9343829 is held at RBC with SWIFT identifier VRAQCA5M. The originating customer's email is fcopeland@example.com and phone is 519-339-7813. Beneficiary email on record: josejones@example.com. This communication is protected under Canadian privacy legislation. The account has been temporarily restricted pending review.",
    "doc_type": "WIRE_TRANSFER",
    "entities": [
      [
        51,
        66,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        164,
        177,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        293,
        314,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        371,
        392,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        328,
        340,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        101,
        118,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        192,
        209,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        72,
        92,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        221,
        224,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        247,
        255,
        "SWIFT"
      ],
      [
        136,
        147,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Personal loan request from Stefany Webb at Royal Bank of Canada. The individual is currently living at 6192 Robert Corner, Hamilton, ON K6R 1X0 and can be contacted at (587) 252-1026 or nfreeman@example.net. They work for Sims, Reeves and Cummings, earning CAD 236,685.00 a year, and are applying for CAD 8,235.00 in personal credit. Their account number is 18173-002-2681675, DOB is 11 November 1971, SIN is 639-446-905. All information has been verified against existing records. The customer acknowledged receipt of this communication.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        27,
        39,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        186,
        206,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        168,
        182,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        103,
        143,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        409,
        420,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        384,
        400,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        43,
        63,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        222,
        247,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        358,
        375,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        301,
        313,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        257,
        271,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        136,
        143,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This letter confirms that SCOTIABANK has completed the mandatory customer identification process for Kerry-Lynn Anderson. Our records show their residential address as 5705 Patricia Loaf, Halifax, NS B2G 2Z2 and their date of birth as October 01, 1989. The social insurance number 363-172-665 has been verified. For correspondence, please use whitneyanderson@example.com or +1 289 382 2264. The account number assigned is 61152-003-9220154, branch transit 63112-016. Internal reference: RER-89885824. Subject to the Proceeds of Crime (Money Laundering) and Terrorist Financing Act.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        101,
        120,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        343,
        370,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        374,
        389,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        168,
        207,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        281,
        292,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        235,
        251,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        26,
        36,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        422,
        439,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        456,
        465,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        200,
        207,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "I, tristian manning, wish to file a formal complaint against CANADIAN WESTERN BANK. An amount of $4,147.00 CAD was charged to my card 6130-4663-4719-6431 without my knowledge. This card is linked to account 46149-016-5033233. I have tried calling 514.587.4989 but could not resolve the issue. Please respond to taylortodd@example.org or in writing to 1599 Young Tunnel, Burnaby, BC V4Y 7C5.",
    "doc_type": "COMPLAINT_LETTER",
    "entities": [
      [
        3,
        19,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        311,
        333,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        247,
        259,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        351,
        389,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        61,
        82,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        207,
        224,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        134,
        153,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        97,
        110,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        382,
        389,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "As part of our regulatory KYC obligations at BMO, we have verified the identity of Ross                           Clark. The customer's date of birth is 20 December 1962, and their social insurance number 715-128-494 has been confirmed. They are currently located at 2677 Hobbs Orchard, Markham, ON P1J 8N2. We have (437) 370-3621 and joshuahoffman@example.org on file. Account 86140-010-1710798 has been opened with transit 22569-010. Electronic records have been updated to reflect the changes. The customer was informed of the outcome via registered mail.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        83,
        119,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        335,
        360,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        316,
        330,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        267,
        306,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        205,
        216,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        153,
        169,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        45,
        48,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        378,
        395,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        425,
        434,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        299,
        306,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Credit application UOP-36385115 received from Alyson Larsen. The applicant confirmed their address as 9285 Patricia Drive, Vancouver, BC V2S 7E9, postal code V2S 7E9. Date of birth is 1975-05-27 and SIN is 403-977-717. Current employer is medina-serrano, annual income CAD$72,291. Loan requested: CAD$190,957. Bank account 25679-010-8711819 at ATB Financial. Best contact: smithjonathan@example.net or call 437-907-4808. Electronic records have been updated to reflect the changes. This communication is protected under Canadian privacy legislation.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        46,
        59,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        373,
        398,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        407,
        419,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        102,
        144,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        206,
        217,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        184,
        194,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        344,
        357,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        239,
        253,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        323,
        340,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        297,
        308,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        269,
        279,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        137,
        144,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        158,
        165,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "Case ref JDO-56056941 — Findlay Thomas notes: spoke to cailyn conway re account 28447-004-1547032 at Desjardins Group. Customer disputing CAD 104,848.00 charge on card 1680-3846-9392-5974. Verified DOB November 07, 1972 and SIN 683-760-706. Address: 1766 Ferguson Stream, Windsor, ON L3W 2N4. Phone: 437.467.8311. Email: kennethjennings@example.org. Escalating to fraud team. Internal audit trail has been updated accordingly.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        55,
        68,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        24,
        38,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        321,
        348,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        300,
        312,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        250,
        291,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        228,
        239,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        202,
        219,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        101,
        117,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        80,
        97,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        168,
        187,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        138,
        152,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        284,
        291,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "During the onboarding process at DESJARDINS GROUP, Amayah                         Smith submitted the required identification documents. The applicant confirmed their address as 5448 Burton Corner, London, ON K3K 6J0 and provided (514) 302-9215 as their primary contact. Their date of birth is 14 May 1995 and their government-issued identification number is 461-574-804. The assigned account number is 69403-002-4134640 and the branch transit is 54113-002. Correspondence may also be directed to gwilson@example.org. Flagged for immediate supervisor review. Coordinating with fraud prevention team on this matter.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        51,
        87,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        497,
        516,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        230,
        244,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        178,
        216,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        359,
        370,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        294,
        305,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        33,
        49,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        403,
        420,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        447,
        456,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        209,
        216,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "The know-your-customer review for rudy                           campbell was completed on 2026-03-22. The customer provided a date of birth of 13 October 1951 and a social insurance number of 331-563-798. Their current residential address is recorded as 5222 James Curve, Barrie, ON N1S 1S0. Contact information on file includes phone number +1 289 428 7787 and email address jasonmartinez@example.com. The customer holds account 41054-030-8878917 with transit number 20253-004 at scotiabank. Reference: MGA-69320178. The file has been marked as high priority. The case has been logged in the internal tracking system.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        34,
        73,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        377,
        402,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        343,
        358,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        255,
        291,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        193,
        204,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        144,
        159,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        482,
        492,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        431,
        448,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        469,
        478,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        284,
        291,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Prepared for brieanna randall — Bank of Nova Scotia account 81505-016-4614847. Statement period: 2026-03-01 to 2026-03-22. Linked card: 9414-5099-1835-5992. Balance: $126,202.00. Available: CAD$23,998. Mailing address on file: 3978 heather lodge, mississauga, on n0r 6w6. Email: escobarbrian@example.net. Tel: 780-798-5825. The customer was informed of the outcome via registered mail. This record is subject to a seven-year retention policy.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        13,
        29,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        279,
        303,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        310,
        322,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        227,
        270,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        32,
        51,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        60,
        77,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        136,
        155,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        166,
        177,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        190,
        200,
        "AMOUNT"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "Note from Trung Meadows: the customer Tesla Young visited our Bank of Montreal branch today and disputed a card charge of $82,946.00 on card 8410-5410-2009-1458 linked to account 13336-003-1902591. I verified their identity using date of birth 28 November 1978 and SIN 388-788-869. Their current address is 9949 Johnson Ford, Quebec City, QC H3C 1C4, postal H3C 1C4. Best contact: bjohnson@example.net and 289.267.9981.",
    "doc_type": "INTERNAL_NOTE",
    "entities": [
      [
        38,
        49,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        10,
        23,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        381,
        401,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        406,
        418,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        307,
        349,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        269,
        280,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        244,
        260,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        62,
        78,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        179,
        196,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        141,
        160,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        122,
        132,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        342,
        349,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        358,
        365,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "I am writing to formally dispute an unauthorized transaction. My name is Bennie Zavala and I have been a customer of CANADIAN WESTERN BANK for several years. On 2026-03-22, I noticed a charge of $471.00 CAD on my card 8521-2136-4059-9185, linked to account 81252-030-6925861. I did not authorize this and request an investigation. I can be reached at +1 905 562 9655 or john75@example.com. My mailing address is 4463 Julie Hills, Sudbury, ON K9X 1X4.",
    "doc_type": "COMPLAINT_LETTER",
    "entities": [
      [
        73,
        86,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        370,
        388,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        351,
        366,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        412,
        449,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        117,
        138,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        257,
        274,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        218,
        237,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        195,
        206,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        442,
        449,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Analyst Simrat Cannon has flagged the account held by Sinead Austin at laurentian bank for suspicious activity. Multiple transactions totalling CAD$434,572 were recorded on account 33900-004-7428879. The customer lives at 6415 Jennings Ports, Montreal, QC H6T 8H3 and can be reached at +1 204 816 3577 or brandonhopkins@example.net. SIN verified as 436-206-411. The pattern does not align with the customer's declared financial profile. Compliance team notified. Retention period of seven years applies per regulatory requirements. This record is protected under the Privacy Act of Canada.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        54,
        67,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        8,
        21,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        305,
        331,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        286,
        301,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        222,
        263,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        349,
        360,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        71,
        86,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        181,
        198,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        144,
        155,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        256,
        263,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
    "text": "This AML report was triggered automatically and reviewed by annabelle                      guzman. The flagged account belongs to Adrian Meadows, born and residing at 4235 Collins Points, Calgary, AB T2T 5L5. Account 93085-006-8531979 at Scotiabank received $199,398.00 CAD in transactions inconsistent with baseline behaviour. Customer contact: +1 825 883 7167 / mary81@example.net. SIN: 437-342-508. Postal: T2T 5L5. Ref: RQE-68202283. The customer's profile has been updated in the core banking system. The transaction has been placed on hold pending investigation.",
    "doc_type": "SAR_MEMO",
    "entities": [
      [
        130,
        144,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        60,
        97,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        364,
        382,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        346,
        361,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        167,
        207,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        389,
        400,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        238,
        248,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        217,
        234,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        258,
        273,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        200,
        207,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        410,
        417,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "Loan file for Harvie Rice: applicant resides at 5112 Hines Trail, Hamilton, ON L6W 5B4 and is employed full-time at love, johnson and morales with verified income of $123,769.00 CAD. Requesting $139,464.00. SIN 273-497-152 confirmed. Born 18/09/1962. Contact: dale78@example.net / +1 519 559 2561. Existing National Bank of Canada account: 71680-004-3826243. Postal code: L6W 5B4. Ref: XBK-01202691. This report is filed under section 7 of the PCMLTFA.",
    "doc_type": "LOAN_APPLICATION",
    "entities": [
      [
        14,
        25,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        260,
        278,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        281,
        296,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        48,
        86,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        211,
        222,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        239,
        249,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        307,
        330,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        116,
        141,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        340,
        357,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        194,
        205,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        166,
        181,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        79,
        86,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ],
      [
        372,
        379,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "This monthly statement has been prepared for agnes mccormick, whose mailing address is 1718 Sullivan Glen, Quebec City, QC H8J 9Z0. The account holder can be contacted at (604) 337-2944 or fullerkristi@example.org. Their primary account at royal bank of canada is 98809-016-6861565, with linked card 9029-7976-2288-8120. The closing balance for this period is $146,488.00, with available credit of CAD$47,389. Flagged for immediate supervisor review. Supporting documentation is available upon request.",
    "doc_type": "ACCOUNT_STATEMENT",
    "entities": [
      [
        45,
        60,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        189,
        213,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        171,
        185,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        87,
        130,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        240,
        260,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        264,
        281,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        300,
        319,
        "CREDIT_CARD"
      ],
      [
        360,
        371,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        398,
        408,
        "AMOUNT"
      ],
      [
        123,
        130,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "train"
  },
  {
    "text": "As part of our regulatory KYC obligations at HSBC Canada, we have verified the identity of taliah schaefer. The customer's date of birth is 08 March 1961, and their social insurance number 137-373-429 has been confirmed. They are currently located at 1744 Figueroa Street, Hamilton, ON M4L 5J7. We have +1 780 842 3180 and butlerashley@example.org on file. Account 67749-039-9389302 has been opened with transit 14225-003. A case number has been assigned for tracking purposes. The customer's profile has been updated in the core banking system.",
    "doc_type": "KYC",
    "entities": [
      [
        91,
        106,
        "PERSON"
      ],
      [
        323,
        347,
        "EMAIL"
      ],
      [
        303,
        318,
        "PHONE"
      ],
      [
        251,
        293,
        "ADDRESS"
      ],
      [
        189,
        200,
        "SIN"
      ],
      [
        140,
        153,
        "DOB"
      ],
      [
        45,
        56,
        "ORG"
      ],
      [
        365,
        382,
        "ACCOUNT_NO"
      ],
      [
        412,
        421,
        "TRANSIT_NO"
      ],
      [
        286,
        293,
        "POSTAL_CODE"
      ]
    ],
    "split": "test"
  },
  {
